{
    "Questions": [
        {
            "Question": "Everything in React is a?",
            "Option1": "Module",
            "Option2": "Component",
            "Option3": "Package",
            "Option4": "Class",
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "Question": "In which directory React Components are saved?",
            "Option1": "Inside js/components/",
            "Option2": "Inside vendor/components/",
            "Option3": "Inside external/components/",
            "Option4": "Inside vendor/",
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "Question": "What is Babel?",
            "Option1": "A transpiler",
            "Option2": "An interpreter",
            "Option3": "A compiler",
            "Option4": "Both Compiler and Transpiler",
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3
        },
        {
            "Question": "What is the capital of Spain?",
            "Option1": "Berlin",
            "Option2": "Buenos Aires",
            "Option3": "Madrid",
            "Option4": "San Juan",
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2
        },
        {
            "Question": "In React what is used to pass data to a component from outside?",
            "Option1": "SetState",
            "Option2": "Render with arguments",
            "Option3": "Props",
            "Option4": "PropTypes",
            "correctAnswerIndex": 2
        },
        {
            "Question": "What type of apps can you build using React Native?",
            "Option1": "Hybrid apps",
            "Option2": "HTML5 apps",
            "Option3": "Mobile web apps",
            "Option4": "Native mobile apps",
            "correctAnswerIndex": 3
        },
        {
            "Question": "ReactJS uses _____ to increase performance",
            "Option1": "Virtual DOM",
            "Option2": "Original DOM",
            "Option3": "Both of above",
            "Option4": "None of the above",
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "Question": "State in react is?",
            "Option1": "A permanent storage",
            "Option2": "Internal storage of the component",
            "Option3": "Both of above",
            "Option4": "None of the above",
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1
        },
        {
            "Question": "How do you access a function fetch() from a h1 element in JSX?",
            "Option1": "<h1>{fetch()}</h1>",
            "Option2": "<h1>${fetch()}</h1>",
            "Option3": "<h1>{fetch}</h1>",
            "Option4": "<h1>${fetch}</h1>",
            "correctAnswerIndex": 0
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which method in a React Component should you override to stop the component from updating?",
            "Option1": "willComponentUpdate",
            "Option2": "shouldComponentUpdate",
            "Option3": "componentDidUpdate",
            "Option4": "componentDidMount",
            "correctAnswerIndex": 1
        }
    ]
}
